# JAMES LA

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### CONTACT

+64 21 174 9208

jamesla200210@gmail.com

Wellington, New Zealand

### SKILLS

- Communication
- · Decision Making
- Time Management
- · Desire to Learn
- Leadership
- Adaptability

# LANGUAGES/ SOFTWARES

Python

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

Unreal Engine

Java

C++

Blender

# LANGUAGES

English

Korean

### **PROJECTS**

### **RESTful Web Application**

VUW - NWEN304 - Group (2 People)

In this group project, my group and I were tasked in creating, deploying and testing a Web Application using Web Application Frameworks and middleware technologies.

Using HTML/CSS/JavaScript and frameworks such as Express.js, we created a website and hosted it on Google Cloud. We were required to implement advanced technologies for developing RESTful Web Applications, including MVC, distributed authentication and authorization, secure data communication, web caching and content replication. At the end, we were required to present the application with a demo and a presentation.

# **CNN Image Classification**

VUW - COMP309 - Individual

Given a dataset of 4,500 images which could be split into three classes, I was required to create a Deep Convolutional Neural Network for Image Classification using Python and Python libraries like Pytorch and Sklearn.

The aim of this project was to evaluate CNNs through the lens of a challenging image classification task by proficiently utilizing available data for model training and hyperparameter tuning, implementing CNNs, applying these pre-trained models to classify unseen test data, and exploring the nuances of different loss functions and optimization techniques tailored for training CNNs. In doing so, I acquired knowledge and expertise in employing various techniques to boost performance on CNNs.

## **Space Hunters**

VUW - CGRA252 - Group (5 People)

As a group, we created a 3D game using Unreal Engine 5. Using free assets online, we developed Space Hunters, a 3D Platformer where the goal of the game was to traverse the map and reach the end, where there would be a boss that the player is required to eliminate.

My role, in this project, was to create the final boss. Here I created a non-player character that would shoot projectiles at the player while tracking him. I also implemented boss stages using enumerators and a health system that was made from sratch.

# JAMES LA

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### EDUCATION

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

# Victoria University of Wellington (VUW)

2020-2024

#### **Notable Courses:**

- COMP307 Introduction to Artificial Networks
  - Developed Machine Learning models from KNN to Deep Neural Networks using Python without libraries like Scikit-Learn.
- COMP309 Machine Learning Tools/Techniques
  - Preprocessed data to train and test Machine Learning models such as K-Nearest Neighbour classifier to Convolutional Neural Networks for Image Classification using Python and Scikit-Learn.
- NWEN304 Advanced Network Applications
  - Developed a secure, scalable and reliable RESTful Web Application by using frameworks, MVC, distributed authentication and authorization to build, deploy and test web applications on a cloud computing infrastructure.
- CGRA352 Image-based Graphics
  - Manipulating images through techniques from, filtering based image processing, to feature matching and image warping.
  - o Expected June 2024

-----

### SOCIALS



www.linkedin.com/in/james-la-36565828b



www.github.com/localbusdriver

\_\_\_\_\_

### REFERENCES

Available upon request

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Cityfitness Receptionist**

CityFitness

06/2023 - Present

- · Processing payments and maintaining accurate records.
- · Greeting and checking in members and guests.
- Answering phone inquiries and providing customer service.
- Maintaining a clean and organized reception area.
- · Assisting with the maintenance of gym equipment.
- Troubleshooting and resolving customer complaints and issues.

#### Kitchen Assistant

Kazu Yakitori and Sake Bar

04/2021 - 06/2022

- Often cooking in high intensity environments.
- Preparing meal ingredients to cook, which includes washing, peeling, cutting, and slicing ingredients.
- Maintaining health and safety procedures by ensuring the cleanliness of the kitchen.
- · Often assisting front of hall staff as required.
- Maintaining organized and sanitary working environments.
- Ensuring orders are being served within thirty minutes of receiving the order.